{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306271334","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306271334"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 31c1d91d-61b4-47a9-8877-84d5ff27a25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tena_fisi-zake-za-tena"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" tena"," userResponse":" tena"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306290571","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306290569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 31c1d91d-61b4-47a9-8877-84d5ff27a25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" tena_fisi-zake-za-tena"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306290692","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306290692"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 31c1d91d-61b4-47a9-8877-84d5ff27a25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306300491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306300490"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306301122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306301122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306301916","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306301915"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306303088","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306303087"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANAISHI"," userResponse":" PANAISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306303546","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306303546"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306304333","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306304333"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306306747","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306306746"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306307585","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306307584"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306308434","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306308433"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306309083","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306309083"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306309317","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306309316"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306310055","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306310054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADOA"," userResponse":" MADOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306310900","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306310900"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEUSI"," userResponse":" MEUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306311105","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306311104"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306311929","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306311929"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEUPE"," userResponse":" MEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306312524","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306312524"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306313061","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306313061"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306313901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306313901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306316710","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306316710"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306317457","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306317456"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306318515","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306318514"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPOENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306319473","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306319473"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZINI"," userResponse":" KAZINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306320682","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306320680"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAACHA"," userResponse":" ANAACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306321304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306321303"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306322075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306322074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZI"," userResponse":" WAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306325234","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306325233"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306326193","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306326192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKAA"," userResponse":" ANAKAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306327303","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306327302"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306327390","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306327390"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306328269","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306328269"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306328877","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306328876"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306329763","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306329762"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUILINDA"," userResponse":" KUILINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306330315","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306330315"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306330532","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306330532"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306331011","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306331010"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306331798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306331798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306334732","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306334731"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306334927","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306334927"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306335737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306335737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306337161","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306337161"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIKARIBIA"," userResponse":" AKIKARIBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306338136","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306338136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306339987","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306339986"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKODOLEA"," userResponse":" ANAMKODOLEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306340696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306340695"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306341242","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306341242"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306342657","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306342657"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUNYOOSHEA"," userResponse":" KUMUNYOOSHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306343382","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306343381"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHA"," userResponse":" KUCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306344165","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306344164"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306347063","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306347062"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306348589","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306348589"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATOROKA"," userResponse":" ANATOROKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306348884","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306348883"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306349556","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306349555"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306350013","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306350012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306353457","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306353457"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306355075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306355074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITOKEZEA"," userResponse":" AKITOKEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306356431","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306356431"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306356696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306356696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YU"," userResponse":" YU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306357693","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306357693"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306359175","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306359174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMKWARUZA"," userResponse":" KUMKWARUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306362536","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306362535"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306363703","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306363703"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAGEUKA"," userResponse":" ANAGEUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306364447","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306364446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" MBIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306365053","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306365052"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306365617","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306365616"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306366160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306366159"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306369381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306369381"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306370309","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306370308"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIHISI"," userResponse":" AKIHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306371057","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306371056"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306372366","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306372365"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFUNGA"," userResponse":" ANAFUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306373130","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306373130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306373385","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306373385"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306374873","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306374872"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUSUKUMA"," userResponse":" KUUSUKUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306378523","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306378522"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAINGIA"," userResponse":" ANAINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306379159","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306379158"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306379393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306379392"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306379990","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306379990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306380779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306380778"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306381530","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306381529"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" CHAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306384854","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306384852"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306386441","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306386440"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIMALIZA"," userResponse":" AKIMALIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306387830","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306387830"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANARUKA"," userResponse":" ANARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306388547","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306388546"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306388797","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306388797"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306389396","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306389395"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOFA"," userResponse":" SOFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306389623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306389622"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306390470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306390470"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306393791","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306393791"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unachosikia ni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNACHOSIKIA"," userResponse":" UNACHOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306394175","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306394174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unachosikia ni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306395121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306395121"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unachosikia ni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PURR"," userResponse":" PURR"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306398222","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306398220"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306399188","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306399187"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306400707","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306400706"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWASILI"," userResponse":" AKIWASILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306401724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306401723"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306403164","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306403164"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJINYOOSHA"," userResponse":" HUJINYOOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306404994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306404993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306406159","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306406159"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306406440","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306406440"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306407733","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306407733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMKARIBISHA"," userResponse":" KUMKARIBISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306408777","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306408777"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306411751","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306411750"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306412437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306412437"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306412651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306412651"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306413262","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306413262"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306414438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306414437"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAKETI"," userResponse":" WANAKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306415135","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306415134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306415420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306415419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306416345","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306416345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306417456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306417455"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306418333","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306418333"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306419554","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306419553"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKISOMA"," userResponse":" AKISOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306420843","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306420843"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GAZETI"," userResponse":" GAZETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306423318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306423316"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306423449","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306423448"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" a506e28d-fa85-47df-9161-0644075acc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GAZETI"," userResponse":" GAZETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306432700","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306432700"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" b08dcdbe-c0a3-4581-befd-5b0e49a06a1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306432799","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306432799"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" b08dcdbe-c0a3-4581-befd-5b0e49a06a1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306432861","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306432861"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" b08dcdbe-c0a3-4581-befd-5b0e49a06a1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306446315","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306446314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c8bbddf5-cc2f-4753-9e61-8060754c91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-14"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306453832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306453832"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c8bbddf5-cc2f-4753-9e61-8060754c91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-16-13"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306460135","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306460135"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c8bbddf5-cc2f-4753-9e61-8060754c91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306465980","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306465980"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c8bbddf5-cc2f-4753-9e61-8060754c91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306471948","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306471948"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c8bbddf5-cc2f-4753-9e61-8060754c91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_16-3-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306484605","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306484605"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c8bbddf5-cc2f-4753-9e61-8060754c91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_9-6-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306491576","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306491576"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c8bbddf5-cc2f-4753-9e61-8060754c91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306512376","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306512376"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c8bbddf5-cc2f-4753-9e61-8060754c91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_13-6-14"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306543436","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306543436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c8bbddf5-cc2f-4753-9e61-8060754c91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_6_13-6-14"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306554597","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306554597"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 25646163-4175-4fec-9123-d4baa119e272"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BARABARA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306558653","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306558653"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 25646163-4175-4fec-9123-d4baa119e272"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BARABARA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306560324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306560323"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 25646163-4175-4fec-9123-d4baa119e272"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BENDERA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BENDERA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306560348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306560348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 25646163-4175-4fec-9123-d4baa119e272"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BENDERA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BENDERA"," userResponse":" BENDERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306572426","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306572426"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 25646163-4175-4fec-9123-d4baa119e272"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BENDERA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306572520","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306572520"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 25646163-4175-4fec-9123-d4baa119e272"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BENDERA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BENDERA"," userResponse":" BENDERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306583911","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306583911"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BARABARA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306588411","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306588411"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BARABARA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306589994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306589993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BENDERA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BENDERA"," userResponse":" BENDERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306593297","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306593297"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BENDERA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BENDERA"," userResponse":" BENDERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306594912","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306594912"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BARIDI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306599279","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306599278"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BARIDI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306600882","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306600882"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BEGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" BEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306604075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306604074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BEGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" BEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306605640","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306605640"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BATA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306608385","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306608385"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BATA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306609992","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306609991"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BUIBUI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306613111","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306613110"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BUIBUI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306614739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306614738"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BABA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306617080","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306617080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BABA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306618714","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306618714"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BABU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABU"," userResponse":" BABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306622374","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306622373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BABU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306623973","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306623973"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BASI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306627209","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306627208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BASI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306628808","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306628808"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BODABODA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BODABODA"," userResponse":" BODABODA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306633806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306633805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BODABODA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BODABODA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306635184","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306635184"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BAISIKELI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BAISIKELI"," userResponse":" BODABODA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306635400","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306635399"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BAISIKELI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISIKELI"," userResponse":" BAISIKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306655642","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306655642"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BAISIKELI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306655734","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306655734"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" c0f968a9-b805-461c-b987-9d4328f19b56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" BAISIKELI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISIKELI"," userResponse":" BAISIKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306665671","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306665671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306666056","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306666055"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306666709","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306666708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306666916","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306666916"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306667823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306667823"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306670145","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306670144"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nichague gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NICHAGUE"," userResponse":" NICHAGUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306671207","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306671205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nichague gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306673949","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306673948"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie ndege?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306675029","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306675029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie ndege?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306675758","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306675757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie ndege?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306678645","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306678644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306679627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306679627"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INARUKA"," userResponse":" INARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306680330","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306680330"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306681097","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306681096"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306683328","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306683327"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa kuruka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306684103","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306684103"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa kuruka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOGOPA"," userResponse":" NAOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306684569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306684568"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa kuruka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306689392","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306689391"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nitumie helikopta?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306690174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306690174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nitumie helikopta?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306691310","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306691310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nitumie helikopta?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306694321","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306694320"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306695174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306695174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306695396","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306695396"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306695773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306695773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306695930","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306695930"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306696564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306696564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306699527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306699527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306700450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306700449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306701368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306701367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" NITATUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306702011","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306702011"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306702095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306702095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306702659","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306702659"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOSHI"," userResponse":" MOSHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306705970","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306705969"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306706835","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306706834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" STESHENI"," userResponse":" STESHENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306707277","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306707277"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306707926","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306707926"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306708503","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306708502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306711259","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306711258"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitachoka kutembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITACHOKA"," userResponse":" NITACHOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306712105","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306712104"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitachoka kutembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306715041","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306715040"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306716223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306716223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306716996","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306716996"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306720229","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306720228"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306720671","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306720671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306721062","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306721062"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" KINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306721508","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306721507"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306721962","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306721961"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306722679","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306722678"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306725949","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306725948"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306727047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306727047"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" NITATUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306727436","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306727436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306728391","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306728390"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306731659","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306731658"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306732506","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306732504"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306733466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306733465"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASA"," userResponse":" HASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306734390","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306734389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306734493","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306734493"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306735212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306735211"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBEBEA"," userResponse":" KUBEBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306735898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306735898"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306736623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306736623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZITO"," userResponse":" MIZITO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306739420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306739419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306740774","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306740773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306741593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306741592"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISKELI"," userResponse":" BAISKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306742803","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306742802"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306745952","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306745951"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIJUI"," userResponse":" SIJUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306746495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306746494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306746826","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306746823"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306747796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306747795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATANIPATIA"," userResponse":" ATANIPATIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306748573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306748572"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISKELI"," userResponse":" BAISKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306749179","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306749179"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306752038","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306752037"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306752760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306752760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIJARIBU"," userResponse":" NIJARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306753503","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306753503"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306753726","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306753725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306754474","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306754474"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUA"," userResponse":" MASHUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306757609","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306757608"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306757975","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306757975"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306758696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306758696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAMINI"," userResponse":" SIAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306759282","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306759282"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUA"," userResponse":" MASHUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306759868","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306759868"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306762714","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306762712"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AAH"," userResponse":" AAH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306765332","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306765331"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306766810","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306766809"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKACHOTUMIA"," userResponse":" NITAKACHOTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306770205","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306770204"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" NITATUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306770891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306770891"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TREKTA"," userResponse":" TREKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306771979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306771978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306774812","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306774811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306774914","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306774914"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 08ac945e-fff4-4c12-a721-cf3f3ce59cab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306783107","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306783107"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 0d10aef3-f426-447f-a399-d86bd89d528e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-Z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306786639","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306786638"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 0d10aef3-f426-447f-a399-d86bd89d528e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_CH-J-B"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306789852","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306789852"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 0d10aef3-f426-447f-a399-d86bd89d528e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_U-B-L"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306792782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306792782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 0d10aef3-f426-447f-a399-d86bd89d528e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-W-M"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306795807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306795807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 0d10aef3-f426-447f-a399-d86bd89d528e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-CH-W"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306798807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306798807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 0d10aef3-f426-447f-a399-d86bd89d528e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-CH-P"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306803562","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306803562"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 0d10aef3-f426-447f-a399-d86bd89d528e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_D-H-B"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306806871","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306806871"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 0d10aef3-f426-447f-a399-d86bd89d528e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_I-T-B"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306810205","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306810205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 0d10aef3-f426-447f-a399-d86bd89d528e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_G-CH-B"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306815252","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306815252"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 0d10aef3-f426-447f-a399-d86bd89d528e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_G-CH-B"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306819381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306819381"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 0d10aef3-f426-447f-a399-d86bd89d528e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_I-G-B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306825114","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306825112"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 0d10aef3-f426-447f-a399-d86bd89d528e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_B_I-G-B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306839389","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306839388"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 3eb589df-1d85-4cd0-a112-482105a67b06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-12-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306845345","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306845345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 3eb589df-1d85-4cd0-a112-482105a67b06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-12-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306852315","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306852315"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 3eb589df-1d85-4cd0-a112-482105a67b06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_11-14-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306858777","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306858777"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 3eb589df-1d85-4cd0-a112-482105a67b06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_11-14-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306867900","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306867900"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 3eb589df-1d85-4cd0-a112-482105a67b06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-4-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306874654","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306874654"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 3eb589df-1d85-4cd0-a112-482105a67b06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-4-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306891485","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306891485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 3eb589df-1d85-4cd0-a112-482105a67b06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-11-13"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306897103","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306897103"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 3eb589df-1d85-4cd0-a112-482105a67b06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_3-10-11"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306903299","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306903299"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 3eb589df-1d85-4cd0-a112-482105a67b06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_3-10-11"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306909113","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306909113"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 3eb589df-1d85-4cd0-a112-482105a67b06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-10-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306914686","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306914685"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 3eb589df-1d85-4cd0-a112-482105a67b06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-12-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306919960","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306919960"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 3eb589df-1d85-4cd0-a112-482105a67b06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-11-14"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306924951","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306924951"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 3eb589df-1d85-4cd0-a112-482105a67b06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-14-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306943805","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306943805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 3eb589df-1d85-4cd0-a112-482105a67b06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-14-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306953316","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306953316"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 3eb589df-1d85-4cd0-a112-482105a67b06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_11-5-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306970928","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306970927"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 3eb589df-1d85-4cd0-a112-482105a67b06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_11-5-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306977407","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306977407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 3eb589df-1d85-4cd0-a112-482105a67b06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_11-5-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306984499","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306984498"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 3eb589df-1d85-4cd0-a112-482105a67b06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_11_11-5-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306996065","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306996065"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 8dad2e99-bdaf-42dd-92a5-64e18b7a6de3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_F-B-T"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548306999101","data":{"timestamp":" 1548306999101"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 8dad2e99-bdaf-42dd-92a5-64e18b7a6de3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-W-A"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307001818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307001817"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 8dad2e99-bdaf-42dd-92a5-64e18b7a6de3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-F-I"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307005076","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307005076"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 8dad2e99-bdaf-42dd-92a5-64e18b7a6de3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_R-N-B"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307008248","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307008247"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 8dad2e99-bdaf-42dd-92a5-64e18b7a6de3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_N-T-B"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307011470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307011470"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 8dad2e99-bdaf-42dd-92a5-64e18b7a6de3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_R-B-J"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307014214","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307014214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 8dad2e99-bdaf-42dd-92a5-64e18b7a6de3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-F-K"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307017369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307017369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 8dad2e99-bdaf-42dd-92a5-64e18b7a6de3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_N-B-Z"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307020662","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307020662"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 8dad2e99-bdaf-42dd-92a5-64e18b7a6de3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_G-F-B"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307023876","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307023876"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 8dad2e99-bdaf-42dd-92a5-64e18b7a6de3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_E-K-B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307029617","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307029617"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 8dad2e99-bdaf-42dd-92a5-64e18b7a6de3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_B_E-K-B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307039322","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307039321"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307039567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307039567"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307040017","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307040016"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307040231","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307040230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307040982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307040981"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307044062","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307044062"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307044925","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307044925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANARUKA"," userResponse":" ANARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307045462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307045461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307046206","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307046206"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307046551","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307046551"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307049643","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307049642"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307050819","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307050818"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESHIKIWA"," userResponse":" AMESHIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307051295","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307051295"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307051555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307051555"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307052309","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307052308"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307052730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307052729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307055736","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307055736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307056372","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307056371"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307057194","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307057194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307058028","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307058027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307061046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307061046"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307062068","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307062067"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWAAGA"," userResponse":" ANAWAAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307062672","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307062672"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307063222","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307063222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307066363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307066363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307067229","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307067228"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOSHA"," userResponse":" ANAOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307067844","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307067844"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYOMBA"," userResponse":" VYOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307068685","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307068684"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" JIKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307071618","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307071618"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307072761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307072760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANAANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307073859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307073859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAONI"," userResponse":" UBAONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307077129","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307077129"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307077963","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307077962"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307078895","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307078895"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307079761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307079761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307083091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307083090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307083399","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307083399"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307083959","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307083958"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307086613","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307086613"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307087624","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307087624"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANALALA"," userResponse":" ANALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307090751","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307090751"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307092401","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307092400"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMZUNGUMZIA"," userResponse":" ANAMZUNGUMZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307093027","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307093026"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307096002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307096001"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307097272","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307097271"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" ANAFIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307100132","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307100131"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307100247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307100247"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" baf96252-44c1-411a-960e-284ddae16109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" ANAFIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307110602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307110602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307113186","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307113186"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307114722","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307114722"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307117710","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307117710"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307119260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307119260"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307122134","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307122134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307123689","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307123689"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307126462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307126462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307128013","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307128013"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307130957","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307130957"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307132517","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307132516"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307135498","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307135498"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307137049","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307137049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307139896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307139895"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307141445","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307141444"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307144427","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307144427"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307145978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307145978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307149315","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307149315"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307150870","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307150870"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307153907","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307153907"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307155476","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307155476"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307155482","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307155482"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307165104","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307165104"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307165222","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307165222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 77d8c5fd-8c36-483b-be9c-6ceb97b37959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307177614","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307177614"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307180173","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307180173"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307181705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307181705"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307184676","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307184676"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307186224","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307186224"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307189098","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307189098"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307190655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307190655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307193300","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307193300"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307194857","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307194857"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307197796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307197796"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307199345","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307199345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307202336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307202336"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307203894","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307203894"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307206627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307206626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307208187","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307208187"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307211072","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307211072"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307212618","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307212618"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307215939","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307215939"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307217509","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307217509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307220855","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307220855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307222402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307222402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307225772","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307225772"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307227329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307227329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307230579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307230579"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307232135","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307232135"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307235289","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307235289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307236857","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307236856"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307239859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307239859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307241424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307241424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307244424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307244424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307245973","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307245973"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307249382","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307249382"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307250933","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307250933"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307253824","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307253824"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307255397","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307255397"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307258640","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307258640"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307260204","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307260204"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307263218","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307263218"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307264767","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307264767"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307267512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307267512"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307269067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307269066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307272121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307272121"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307273685","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307273685"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307276622","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307276622"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307278183","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307278183"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307281338","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307281338"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307282905","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307282905"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307286053","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307286053"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307288065","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307288064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307288233","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307288233"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_080321"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}